workamajig.com 2018-12-24

# Workamajig Privacy Policy

By using or accessing this website you are agreeing to the Privacy Policy set forth below.

You may browse our site anonymously without indicating any personal data. We may ask you to disclose personal data for orders, to register products and services and/or send us a question or comment via our Contact Form. We do not require anyone, regardless of age, to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary.

If you do provide us with personal information for some reason, we don’t automatically list your information internally as a candidate to receive future emails from our company. However, we may email you in the future if we feel it to be of a nature that is warranted. You may let us know if you do not wish to receive emails in the future by contacting us using the Contact Form.

Any personal information that is retained will not be rented, sold or otherwise distributed to unrelated third parties. We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of any personal information but will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.

This site may use cookies for site administration purposes. If you do not want to take advantage of the use of cookies, please modify your browser so that it does not accept them. If you've previously consented to cookies and now wish to withdraw that consent, please clear your browser's cache.

This website may detect and use your IP address or domain name for internal traffic monitoring and capacity purposes or to otherwise administer our website. No personal information is obtained, rather just the patterns of usage of our various users.

We may also collect and store information about your visit on an anonymous, aggregate basis. This information may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We may also record the name of your Internet service provider. We use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving our sites.

Our company reserves the right to disclose user information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other website users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.

Our company encourages parents/guardians to monitor and take a part in children’s online activities. No information should be submitted to this site by users less than 13 years of age.

Our company doesn’t knowingly collect information from our guests under 13 years of age and does not provide any personally identifying information from such guests to any third party for any reason whatsoever. We do not allow guests that are known to be under 13 years of age to receive direct marketing communications from our company or from affiliated third parties.

If you are a parent/guardian, you may contact our company to inquire as to personal information submitted by a child less than 13 years of age and, if there indeed is information in our files, you may ask to have it deleted and ask to not allow further collection or use of the child’s information. Parents and guardians have the option to agree to the collection and use of a child’s information without providing additional consents.

Please be advised that our website may contain links to third-party websites. The linked sites are not under the control of our company, and we are not responsible for the contents or privacy practices of any linked site or any link on a linked site.

We will revise or update this Privacy Policy as it deems appropriate, including for example, if our practices change, as we change existing or add new services, as we develop better ways to inform you of products we think will be of interest, or if the law so requires. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
